{
    "id": "5e15c29af8e241aeb1ab08f36cd76b73",
    "title": "Fairly, Quite, Rather, Pretty",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "599a6ff4e6ca485ebd9413bfb62514b4",
            "title": "Fairly, Quite, Rather, And Pretty",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Your handwriting is ……………….. good, but you can improve it.",
                    "description": "If something is fairly good, it is not very good. It is satisfactory. \r\nFairly does not suggest a very high degree.\r\n",
                    "answers": [
                        "fairly",
                        "quite",
                        "rather",
                        "pretty"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ………………………….. tall. He should be able to join the basketball team.",
                    "description": "If he is quite or rather tall, then height will not be an issue at all. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "fairly",
                        "rather",
                        "quite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My room looks ……………………….. neat and tidy. I don’t have to clean it for at least a week.",
                    "description": "Either quite or rather can be used here. Both of them express a higher degree than fairly. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "fairly",
                        "quite",
                        "rather"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The exam was ……………………. difficult. I don’t think that I will pass.",
                    "description": "Either quite or rather can be used here. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "fairly",
                        "rather",
                        "quite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "His books are ………………………….. difficult to understand. I don’t enjoy reading them at all.",
                    "description": "Rather and quite indicate a very high degree.",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather",
                        "fairly",
                        "quite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She can speak German ………………….. fluently. People often think she is German.",
                    "description": "Rather and quite indicate a very high degree.",
                    "answers": [
                        "quite",
                        "rather",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is ……………………… foolish of you to behave like that.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "quite",
                        "rather",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her speeches are ………………………… interesting. I make it a point to listen to them.",
                    "description": "Rather suggests a very higher degree than fairly.",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather",
                        "fairly",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our team’s performance was ……………………….. a disappointment.",
                    "description": "Both quite and rather can modify nouns and verbs.",
                    "answers": [
                        "pretty",
                        "fairly",
                        "quite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………………….. enjoy her company.",
                    "description": "Rather can modify verbs. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather",
                        "pretty",
                        "fairly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was …………………………. disappointed with my results.",
                    "description": "If you are quite disappointed, then you are really disappointed. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather",
                        "fairly",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better not go out now. It is ………………………….. cold.",
                    "description": "All of these expressions suggest very high degrees of something. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather",
                        "quite",
                        "pretty",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}